<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>DeepSketch. Make your own artwork!</title>
    <link>https://gepettolab.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on DeepSketch. Make your own artwork!</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>ko-kr</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 19:40:53 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://gepettolab.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy</title>
      <link>https://gepettolab.github.io/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 19:40:53 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gepettolab.github.io/privacy/</guid>
      <description>Privacy Policy Welcome to DeepSketch (“DeepSketch,” “we,” “us” or “our”). DeepSketch provides a fast, beautiful way for you to sketch-like-stylize your photo. Just snap a photo, choose a filter to transform the look and feel, and share!
Our Privacy Policy explains how we and some of the companies we work with collect, use, share and protect information in relation to our mobile services, web site, and any software provided on or in connection with DeepSketch services (collectively, the “Service”), and your choices about the collection and use of your information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Improved filter speed by 30%</title>
      <link>https://gepettolab.github.io/blog/2018/06/23/speedup/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jun 2018 08:59:06 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gepettolab.github.io/blog/2018/06/23/speedup/</guid>
      <description> Change Logs  Improved filter speed by 30%. Improved app stability.  install  Android: playstore iOS: appstore  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to DeepSketch</title>
      <link>https://gepettolab.github.io/blog/2018/06/13/intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2018 16:09:31 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gepettolab.github.io/blog/2018/06/13/intro/</guid>
      <description>What is DeepSketch Sketches like art! We will make your picture a wonderful sketch. A nice sketch created by artificial intelligence
Using the mobile-optimized artificial intelligence (Deep Learning) technology, you can create beautiful sketch artworks that look like people&amp;rsquo;s drawings.
 Select the desired picture and apply the sketch filter below to sketch the picture. You can save the sketch image or share it with an SNS such as an Instagram.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://gepettolab.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gepettolab.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>We are here to help you Are you curious about something? Do you have some kind of problem with our products? We do not yet have a service organization. Developers will review, identify and answer your questions and questions directly.
Please feel free to contact us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAQ</title>
      <link>https://gepettolab.github.io/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gepettolab.github.io/faq/</guid>
      <description>Pellentesque habitant morbi tristique senectus et netus et malesuada fames ac turpis egestas. Vestibulum tortor quam, feugiat vitae, ultricies eget, tempor sit amet, ante. Donec eu libero sit amet quam egestas semper. Aenean ultricies mi vitae est. Mauris placerat eleifend leo.
1. WHAT TO DO IF I HAVE STILL NOT RECEIVED THE ORDER? Pellentesque habitant morbi tristique senectus et netus et malesuada fames ac turpis egestas. Vestibulum tortor quam, feugiat vitae, ultricies eget, tempor sit amet, ante.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>